Finding Aid for Provost (University of Michigan) records, 1934-1951
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Special Service Personnel
  - Administrative function (Box 4)
  - Class specifications (correspondence) (Box 5)
  - Class specifications (preliminary reports) [2 folders] (Box 5)
  - Class specifications (procedures manual) (Box 5)
  - Class specifications (drafts and revisions) [2 folders] (Box 5)
  - Salary charts (Box 5)
  - Report of Educational Policies Committee (Box 5)
  - Position description forms (Box 5)
  - Salary scale (proposed) (Box 5)
  - University relations (summary) (Box 5)
  - Preliminary survey (Box 5)
- Counseling Project
  - Letters and function lists (Box 5)
  - Dean of students; dean of women; other institutions (Box 5)
- John A. Perkins files
  - Aeronautical Research Center (Willow Run Research Center) (Box 15)
  - Engineering Research Institute (Box 15)
  - Family Living Program (Box 15)
  - Nursing Survey Meeting (Box 15)
  - Phoenix Project (Box 15)
  - Research (Box 15)
  - Retirement Systems (Box 15)